# **GERMAN DOJCINOVIC**

# Software Engineer

### SUMMARY

From the day I wrote my first line of code, I knew that software development wouldn't be "just a job". It rather became a full-fledged passion that only gets more exciting as the time goes by. As a driven and detail-oriented front-end engineer, I am able to bring my expertise and enthusiasm to every project I work on.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Software Engineer at Lumen Spei Digital DOO

#### December 2022 — Present

Collaborating with a team of developers to build modern and responsive web and mobile applications using best practices.

## **Recent Projects:**

**Factiiv CRM (Fullstack Web App)** – Factiiv is the first-ever credit reporting platform on the blockchain. Factiiv allows companies to build their business credit by simply connecting and interacting with businesses through their everyday activities.

**Pawtocol (Mobile App)** – Pawtocol is a global online community of pet lovers who aim to disrupt the pet industry by leveraging blockchain technology to monetize data about their pets, improve owners' purchasing experience, and help veterinarians to deliver better care.

# Administrative Assistant at MIR Production, Belgrade, Serbia

2020 - 2022

Managed WordPress website, worked with MS Word documents and communicated with customers.

# **Engineer at Institute of Bioorganic Chemistry, Russian Academy of Sciences**

2017 - 2020

Performed peptide synthesis and laboratory procedures.

### CONTACT

+381 66 559 44 39

germandoicinovic@gmail.com

germandojcinovic.com

github.com/orjive5

linkedin.com/in/german-dojcinovic/

Belgrade, Serbia

# **SKILLS**

HTML

CSS

**Javascript** 

**Typescript** 

React

React Native

**NextJS** 

Git

GitHub

**TailwindCSS** 

Figma

## **EDUCATION**

RTU MIREA, Moscow, Russia

2015 - 2019

**BSc Biotechnology** 

### LANGUAGES

Serbian (native)

Russian (native)

English (fluent)